HADYAN **YUSUF**

Designer

EXPERIENCE

PT. XL AXIATA TBK

2018 - 2022 | USER EXPERIENCE / VISUAL DESIGNER Initially, I worked on the UI Design project for MyXL and Sidompul. Then I moved to work on the XL Axiata website project and the XL.CO.ID website for UI/UX design and microwebsite such as eSIM project and G20.

PT. DIFINI TEKNOLOGI 2018 - 2022 | FRONTEND DEVELOPER

As a Frontend Developer I've been involved in some projects writing the front-end code for responsive system sites based on client needs. The clients I manage are Bank Mandiri and CIMB Niaga.

PT. INDONESIA OPPO ELECTRONICS 2018 - 2022 | WEB DESIGNER

As a Web Designer I am responsible in building responsive web interfaces using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP. Occasionally, I do research, create user flows, sketch wireframes, and create mockups & prototypes.

EDUCATION

2011 - 2015

BINUS UNIVERSITY

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

2009 - 2011

SMA AL-IZHAR PONDOK LABU



ABOUT ME





 □ hadyanyusuf@gmail.com 081990002023

I am a Product Designer specializing in user experience and user interfaces for digital products. I am involved in the product development cycle from product development to product launch for mobile apps and websites. My background is in IT and I have a passion for design so I have mixed experience from technical skills for coding and design knowledge for appearance.

WORK TOOLS











